{
    "id": "687c56ac0b7d45eaabefd26852b348f3",
    "title": "Articles With Uncountable Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We need a secretary with ……………………. knowledge of Spanish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1641181ab8334a8c955047b040f3334a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks ……………………. English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7b63038283da45338de52bf8c139af89"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got …………………… for dry hair?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shampoo",
                "a shampoo",
                "the shampoo"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0a87188c5064da5b200dd2ac95fc18d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been such ……………………… help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "a great",
                "the great"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e3370b8b34a41828d4c531a8c0c741b"
        },
        {
            "question": "All that you need is …………………… sleep.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e11d705eb083485da2cb6f24aa0005b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are having …………………. weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terrible",
                "a terrible",
                "the terrible"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5609fbf795fe4c2c9facf1ec363cb688"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has made …………………… progress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9aadeb6fc4d84fc6bc890ce3bc9a92cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents gave me ………………… education.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8497b02c9d664243ac6e5797701f3e29"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ……………………… understanding of the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65f2c7af29f342d381ff82a0cd62124c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I love listening to ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wind",
                "a wind",
                "the wind"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "393eed677bff4bf095f770551b3eb827"
        }
    ]
}